ILGWU Organizing Department Records 5780/144
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Necessary Objects, NLRB, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Necessary Objects, D and B Reports, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Necessary Objects, election campaign, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Recyclers Consulting Group, press, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Sae Gae Times, press, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Ssang Bang Wool, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- S and W Knitting, anti-ILG, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- S and W Knitting, NLRB, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Knitwear, recognition agreement, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- San Francisco Knitworks, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- San Francisco day care workers, press, 1987-1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- San Francisco day care workers, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Sanmarks/Stardust, 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Sanyo Fashions, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Sara Lee Corporation, accessories: Coach, Mark Cross, Aris Isotoner, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Sara International, S.I. Cutting, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- M. Shapiro and Company, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Shamiana, INC., 1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Soho Manufacturing, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- STX, INC., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Suzette Fashions, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Suzette Fashions, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Suzette Fashions, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Suzette Fashions (El Paso, Texas), 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Talbots, INC., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Teammate Fashion, INC., 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Three Sisters, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Three Sisters, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Three Sisters, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Undergarment Fashions, INC., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- UniHosiery Company/NAFTA-NAO Case, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- UniHosiery Company, civil rights case, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- UniHosiery Company, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- UniHosiery Company, NLRB, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Venture Store INC., 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Wacoal Corporation, 1984-1995 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Warren Corporation (1995 Organizing Campaign), 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- ACTWU, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- ACORN, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Abrams, Robert, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Attorney General
- Acapulco Fashions, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Alabama, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Anti-Union Lawyers, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Appeals Committee, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Appleton, Shelly, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  General Secretary-Treasurer
- Authorization Card, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  English, Spanish, and Portuguese
- B, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Bail-Bond, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Barbizon Corporations, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Benefits, Welfare and Changes, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Beverly Lingerie, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Bills, Paid, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Blue Cross Blue Shield of Arkansas, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Bobbie Brooks, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Booklet Printing, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Boycotts, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Budget, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- C, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- C. B. Sports, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Canada. General, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Canada. Non-Union [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Canada. Non-Union [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Carter's, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Census, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Chaikin, Sol, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Chevette, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Clerks. Problems of Computer Workers, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Cluett Peabody, 1969-1979 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- College town Contractors, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Connecticut Foundry, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Cotrell and Leonard, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Cranston Print Works, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- D, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Dan Howard Industries, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  English and Spanish
- Danahy, Joseph, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Decertification's, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Donovan, Ray, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Dorby Frocks, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- E. R. Moore, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Eileen Hope, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Elk Brands, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  W. E. Stephens
- Films. Catalogs, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Fugazy Continental Corporation, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- G, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Garland, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Glydon's, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Includes notes written on inside of original folder.
- Greatest Teams. Bayside, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Includes notes written on inside of original folder
- Greylock Mountain Industries. Saw Mill River Industries., 1976-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Includes 21 photographs and 21 negatives.
- H, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Hope Industries, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- I, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- ILGWU. Union Membership and Employment, 1959-1979., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Immigration Amnesty Policy, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Industrial Union Department, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Issachar Reuben Report, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- It's a Way of Life, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- J, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- John Meyer, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Jordasche, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Kaiser-Roth Corporation. Gulf and Western (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Kellwood, 1966-1980 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Includes one photograph
- Kullman and Lang, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- L, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Learners Exemptions, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Levi Strauss, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Lind-Clare, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  Lloyd Weber; Scaboo; Lorraine; Lew-Mar. Includes notes written on inside of original folder.
- Lowenstein, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- M, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Matouk Industries, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Matsil Brothers. Keystone Nitewear, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  Includes 10 photographs and notes written on inside of original folder
- Maurice Sylverria, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Ms. Sugar, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- N, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Norma Rae. Kortex Products., 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- O, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- P, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Polar Manufacturing, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- S, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Setlow and Sons, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Spring City Knitting, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Sun Apparel, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- T, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Ursula of Switzerland, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Vassarette, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- W, 1974-1980 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Z, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Zimney, Max, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 46)